♪ After two days ♪
♪ In the desert sun ♪
♪ My skin began to turn red ♪
♪ After three days ♪
♪ In the desert fun ♪
♪ I was lookin' at a riverbed ♪
♪ And the story it told ♪
♪ of a river that flowed ♪
♪ Made me sad to think it was dead ♪
♪ You see, I've been through the desert ♪
♪ on a horse with no name ♪
♪ It felt good to be out of the rain ♪
♪ In the desert you can remember your name ♪
♪ 'Cause there ain't no one for to give you no pain ♪
♪ After nine days, I let the horse run free ♪
早上好  警官
Good morning, Officer.
-先生  能把音乐关小吗   -噢  好的
- Sir, can you turn the music down? - Oh, yeah.
好的
All right.
关小的意思是关掉
Down means off.
当然  好的
Of course. Okay.
知道为什么要你靠边停吗
You know why I pulled you over this morning?
我很  很确定我没有超速
Well, I'm-- I'm pretty sure I wasn't speeding.
我装了定速巡航  所以我...
I've been using the cruise control, so I--
不  先生  是你的挡风玻璃
No, sir. Your windshield.
请出示驾照和行驶证
License and registration, please.
好的
Right.
这...这是515航班造成的
This-- This was from Wayfarer 515.
-我家正好就残骸区中  -好的
- Um, my house was in the debris field. - Okay.
恩  而且
Uh, and that's--
飞机上掉下的碎片
that's what shattered my windshield--
打碎了我的挡风玻璃
some piece of wreckage from the plane.
我明白
I understand.
你知道515航班  那次坠机事件
You know of-- of Flight 515, the plane crash?
-你戴着绶带  -是的  先生
- You're wearing the ribbon.  - Yes, sir.
我非常清楚515航班
I'm quite aware of Wayfarer 515.
我是那天在现场第一批反应过来的一员
I was one of the first responders on the scene that day.
那你现在在做什么
Then what are you doing?
传讯你  先生
Citing you, sir.
什么  什么  你不相信我
What? What, you don't believe me?
先生  不管挡风玻璃是怎么损坏的
Sir, regardless of how that windshield was damaged,
在此情况下驾驶这辆车都是不安全的
this car is unsafe to drive in this condition.
请呆在车里
Stay in the car, please.
等等  等一会  就一会
Wait. Wait just a minute. Just one minute.
先生  我要求你呆在车里
Sir, I asked you to stay in the vehicle.
不  不  不
No, no, no.
-我有权利从自己的车里出来  -先生  听着
- I can get out of my own car. - Sir, listen--
不  不  不  你听我说
No, no, no. You listen to me.
现在是你听我说
It's time for you to listen to me.
先生  你需要做一下深呼吸
Sir, what you need to do is take a deep breath,
-冷静一下  -这是美国
- Calm down. - This is America.
现在回到车里
And get back in that car now.
-我有权利  -你能明白么
- I have rights. - Do you understand that?
至少有起码的礼貌把我的话听完
At least have the common decency to hear me out.
你现在立刻退后
I need you to step back right now.
-你有没有听到我说什么  -先生  冷静
- Did you even hear what I said? - Sir, calm down.
你现在竟然给我开罚单  我告诉过你
Now you're giving me a ticket? I told you
我家就在残骸区
that my house was in the debris field.
你有没有稍微注意到这意味着什么
Do you have the remotest inkling of what that means?
先生  冷静
Sir, calm down.
地狱之火雨点般撒落在我的房子上
Hellfire rained down on my house
-请你立刻后退  -落在我孩子睡觉的地方
- Sir, I need you to step back now. - Where my children sleep!
在我院子里散落着尸体的碎片
There were body parts in my yard!
-先生  最后一次警告你  -你在耍我
- Sir, this is your last warning. - You gotta be kidding me!
你有两秒钟时间退后
You got about two seconds to stand down,
否则我将对你使用胡椒喷雾器
or I'm gonna pepper spray you.
你有胡椒喷雾  棒极了
You're gonna pepper spray? Perfect!
真的是太棒了  对一个在美国宪法保护下
That is just perfect! Pepper spray the man
表达自己观点的人使用胡椒喷雾器
who's expressing his opinion under the First Amendment!
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：叶子飘零     meredith49     灰兔灰兔     silmar
绝
命
毒
师
第三季
第二集
翻译：小路     时间轴：Angelica     特效：Will
■
后期：冰河       校对&监制：蛐蛐
最近  埃尔帕索暗中有些小动作
Lastly, a little something from down El Paso way.
边境巡逻队遇到的多重凶杀案
Border Patrol came across multiple homicides
只是在边境这边
just this side of the border.
出了华雷斯和拉雷
Truck turn out to be a chicken run
卡车就成了小鸡快跑
out of Juarez and Laredo.
边境巡逻队和这些走私贩子
Border Patrol's been playing hide-and-seek
玩了两年捉迷藏
with these polleros for two years.
但是这一次  他们刚一过来
But this time, as soon as they made it across,
有人就攻击了他们  狠狠地攻击了他们
someone hit them-- hit them hard.
我们这里说的是一个司机和九个非法移民
We're talking a driver and nine illegals.
没有枪手的迹象
No sign of the shooters.
这辆客车装的可不仅仅是人
This truck was carrying more than just people.
我们在找什么  烟草  可卡因还是冰毒
What are we looking at? Weed, coke, or meth?
都不是  他们看起来不像是在运输毒品
Nah. Doesn't look like they were transporting narcotics.
那边境巡逻队干嘛踢给我们
So, why did the Border Patrol kick this to us?
他们没踢给我们  是我要过来的
They didn't. I pulled it.
你问我  这是卡特尔集团高层的杰作
You ask me, this's high-end cartel work.
也许是洛泽塔斯团伙
Los Zetas, maybe.
问题是  为什么我们的非军事区
Question is, why do we have Juarez-style action
华雷斯暴行: 墨西哥北部边境奇瓦瓦州的华雷斯Juarez因贩毒和暴力而“闻名”  被人称为“鬼城”  今年以来  已有包括16个警察在内的280人被犯罪集团杀害
会出现华雷斯暴行
on our side of the DMZ?
他们发送消息或清除道路
They sending a message or clearing a path?
或者这是要阻止一场特殊的边界斗争
Or was this about stopping one particular border-hopper?
也许其中一个入境的墨西哥人
Maybe one of those extra-crispies
知道了他不该知道的
knew something he shouldn't.
不管怎么样  眼睛放亮点
Anyway, keep your eyes open.
好吧  就这样  没什么要说的了
All right. That's it. Slow news day.
补充一点
Add one more to the countdown.
哦  什么  格米
Oh, yeah? What's that, Gomie?
我们还等着你那著名的蓝色冰毒的进展呢
We're waiting on that famous blue meth of yours.
自从上次见过它已经过去29天了
29 days since we saw it last.
哦  是啊  仍在逍遥法外  格米  别担心
Yeah, well, it's still out there, Gomie. Don't worry.
当地警察  我得接这个电话
Local PD. I gotta take this.
格米  打你的皮纳塔去吧
Gomie, go beat your Piñata.
Piñata: 挂起来让小孩子挥棒子打的一种东西  打破了就有糖果掉出来
其他聊天打屁的  安静点
Rest of you jokers- too damn quiet in here.
去抓坏蛋
Go catch some bad guys.
施拉德
Schrader.
嘿  保罗  怎么了
Hey, what's up, Paul?
什么
What?
杰西
Jesse?
嗨  爸爸
Hey, Dad.
你在整修这栋房子
So you're fixing up the house, huh?
就小修一下
Doing a little work, yeah.
恩  那我就先走了
Uh, I'll bounce.
做的不错
It's-- It's cool.
你最近好吗
You doing okay?
嗯  我很好
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
我只是开车经过
I just happened to be driving by
看见牌子
and saw the sign.
那你要卖这个地方吗
So, you're selling the place.
在这种经济形势下
In this market.
你能相信吗
Can you believe it?
你把车房给挪了挪  这想法挺大胆
I see you moved the garage. That's bold.
是你母亲的主意  这可是大工程
Your mother's idea. It's quite an operation.
我们粉刷了所有的墙面  所有的主卧室
We did, all new stucco, all the master suite,
喷沙打磨  熏蒸消毒了地下室
sandblasted, fumigated the basement...
好极了
Right on.
是啊
Yeah.
整修一下肯定能提高转售价值
Fixing up the place totally increases resale value.
那是我读到的  我想说的是  就像
I read that in- I want to say, like,
时代周刊里说的
Time magazine.
那楼上浴室你是怎么处理的
So, what'd you do with the upstairs bathroom?
全部重做  浴室和厨房全铺新瓷砖
All redone. New tiles in the bathrooms and kitchens,
花岗岩台面  全新设备
granite countertops, new appliances--
全部是最好的
all top of the line.
天呐  太棒了  爸爸
Damn. That's great, Dad.
我能随便参观一下吗
Think, uh, I can get a tour?
恩  这些师傅正加紧完工呢
Eh, these guys are trying to finish up.
我们最好还是别妨碍他们
Maybe we'd better stay out of their way.
如果你想看看的话
There are pictures on the Web site,
网站上有图片
if you wanna take a look.
好吧
Cool.
你看上去气色不错
You're looking healthy.
我会告诉你母亲的  她会很欣慰的
I'll tell your mother. She'll be happy.
多谢
Thanks.
我想说  我可以时不时的来看望你们
You know, I could come by sometime
吃个晚饭或做点什么别的
for, uh, dinner or something.
好啊
Yeah.
改日吧
Sometime.
好的
Okay.
回见  爸爸
Later, Dad.
你知道的  听着
You know, look,
他是怀恩中学的高中老师
he's a high school teacher over at Wynne.
一辈子从未出过任何乱子
Never been in trouble a day of his life.
后来他发现自己有肺癌
Found out he's got lung cancer,
然后他老婆把他这倒霉蛋从家里踢了出去
and now his wife kicks the poor out of his own house.
我的意思是  兄弟们
I mean, look, guys,
如果说谁心里有点火
if anybody rates a little slack,
也就是他了
here's the guy.
嘿  沃尔特  嗯
Hey, Walt, uh,
你还记得卡瓦诺警官吗
You remember Officer Cavanaugh?
警官  我很抱歉对您发火
Officer, I'm very sorry that I lost my temper.
我的这种行为无法原谅
There's no excuse for my behavior.
太无礼了
It was disrespectful.
她要跟我离婚
She's divorcing me.
我不知道该怎么跟你说  老兄
Oh, I don't know what to tell you, buddy.
事已至此了
It is what it is.
她还不准让我见孩子
She doesn't want me to see the kids.
她是这么说的
She said that?
是的
Yeah.
你没写信也没给我打电话
You don't write? You don't call?
天呐
God.
这是场灾难
It's a disaster.
这不是灾难
It is not a disaster.
-哦  好的  -这不是灾难  行了吧
- Oh, okay. - It's not a disaster, all right?
她不会去告诉警察
She's not going to the cops.
她也不会告诉任何人
She's not gonna tell a living soul.
你想知道为什么吗
You wanna know why?
一个词  利益双关
one word "Blowback."
如果她泄露秘密
If she blabs,
对她来说也是灾难
it'll be a disaster for her.
那个缉毒所的妹夫
That DEA brother-in-law?
也跟着倒霉
Whew! Screwed.
你就在他的眼皮子底下犯事
You were right under his nose.
他要是幸运的话今后也就只能
He'll be lucky if they let him
在消闲商店里抓抓吸毒的
bust glue-sniffers at the hobby shop.
孩子们呢  打电话给菲尔医生说
The kids-- Paging Dr. Phil.
我爸爸是毒贩子  我妈妈把他告发了
My daddy's a drug dealer, and my mommy turned him in.
现在房子也没有了
And the house-- gone.
逮捕她  然后把孩子们都赶出去
RICO her and the kids out on the street.
还要和他们继续争执的话  只能祝你好运了
Good luck arguing with them on that.
不会的  这些都不会发生
No. It's not gonna happen.
她在虚张声势
She's bluffing,
而且她也明白
and she knows it.
她是否去跟警察告密
Her going to the police
这不是重点  索尔
is not the point, Saul.
她要走出我的生活  你明白吗
She's out of my life. Do you understand?
我失去了我的家庭
I've lost my family,
我在乎的一切都没了
everything that I care about.
嘿  兄弟
Hey, buddy,
恩  太糟了
uh, it's bad.
好吧  这是灾难
All right... It's a calamity,
但我们留得青山在  不怕没柴烧
but we live to fight another day.
等过一段时间  风平浪静了
And after a decent interval of time,
然后
Well,
天涯何处无芳草啊
There are other fish in the sea.
你已经有很长时间没在这个圈子里了
You've been out of circulation for a while.
我的意思是  外面的世界很精彩
I mean, you'll be just amazed at what's out there.
泰国妞  捷克妞
Thailand, the Czech Republic...
我是说  那些女人都会万分荣幸
I mean, those women are so grateful
的到这儿来
to even be here.
与此同时呢
In the meantime,
闲则生非
idle hands are the devil's playthings,
所以  你应该重新开始
So, uh, you should get back on the horse
做你最拿手的事
and do what you do best.
第一步  和我们的朋友谈谈并开始制毒
First step, talk to our friend and get cooking.
我不能做坏人
I can't be the bad guy.
什么
What?
我不能做坏人
I can't be the bad guy.
好吧
Okay.
那么  这样吧  我们再联系
You know, we'll, uh-- we'll revisit.
只是  恩
Just, uh,
答应我你不会把自己吊死在壁橱里
Promise me you won't hang yourself in the closet.
爸爸
Pop-pop!
爸爸  卖雪糕的来了
Pop-pop, the ice-cream man!
-别告诉你妈妈哦  -好的
- Don't tell your mom.  - Okay.
-请讲  -是我
- Yeah.  - It's me.
他老婆可能是个麻烦
We may have a wife problem.
给我密切关注这事
Look, I need eyes on it.
你有地址吗
You got an address?
晚饭大概要晚点才能吃了
Hey, dinner's gonna be late.
汉克姨夫和玛丽姨妈带外卖了
Uncle Hank and Aunt Marie are bringing takeout.
如果你饿的话
But, if you're hungry,
我可以先给你弄点简单的吃
I could rustle something up.
好吧
Okay.
把番茄酱拿给我好吗
Hey, buddy, pass the ketchup, will you?
怎么了
What?
我吃够反式脂肪酸了
I've had enough trans fat for one lifetime.
何不开两天车到附近海滩去
A two-day drive from the nearest ocean,
你就能吃到生鱼了
and you're eating raw fish.
这就是我的意见
That's all I'm saying.
那米诺鱼会更新鲜
Been a while since that minnow been swimming.
对吧  老兄
Right, buddy?
你们知道  弗林
You know, um, Flynn, uh, here
正在找兼职
is looking for a part-time job, so...
如果你们有什么消息
I don't know. If you know of anything, you might wanna--
我叫小沃尔特
My-- My name's Walter Jr.
你好像
Like-- Like--
你难道连他的名字都不愿提吗
What, you-- you can't even say his name?
如果你改变主意不想叫弗林了
Um, if you've changed your mind about being called Flynn,
只需告诉我
All you need to do is just tell me
-你不想叫这个名字  -你知道吗
- That you don't want to be called Flynn. - You know what?
爸直到第四节课才来
Dad didn't even show up till fourth period,
他的眼睛都红了
and his eyes were all red
像是哭过了一样
like he'd been crying or something.
但你一点都不关心
But you-- you don't even care.
现在他都不愿送我回家了
And now, he won't even drive me home.
他不说为什么
He won't say why,
但我知道肯定是你从中作梗
But I know it's because you told him not to.
-亲爱的  我  -你什么
- Honey, I  - What?
我不知道你有什么毛病
I don't know what your problem is.
大概你不再爱他了
You may not love him anymore,
但是我爱
But I do.
为什么你非得
I mean, why you gotta be--
非得像个贱人
Why-- Why you gotta be such a-- a bitch?
别这样说
Hey, hey, hey. No, no, no. Oh...
-汉克  -你不能这么和妈妈说话
- Hank-- Hank-- Hank  - You don't talk to your mom that way.
没事
It's-- It's-- It's all right.
斯凯勒  我知道你这样做
Skyler, I know that you must have your reasons
一定有自己的理由
for...all of this.
我
I...
斯凯
Sky, uh,
我知道这不关我的事
I-- I know it's none of my business,
但是
But, uh,
不让沃尔特见孩子...
Keeping Walt from the kids...
你是对的  汉克
You're right, Hank.
这不关你的事
It's none of your business.
我的天
Oh, my God.
到了现在  你还能说
After all of that, please tell me
你对他们的事不好奇吗
That you are still not curious.
没什么可好奇的
There's nothing to be curious about.
拜托
Please.
今天我听说了怀特还有一部手机
The day I heard there was a second cell phone, I knew.
这种事我看过几百次了
Believe me. I've seen it a hundred times.
好吧  那是什么
Okay. All right. So, what?
别卖关子了  到底是什么事
Stop dancing around it. What is it exactly
什么事你看了几百次
that you have seen a hundred times?
告诉我吧
Please, please, enlighten me.
像沃尔特那样的人
Look, a guy like Walt--
你知道的  好好先生  正直  聪明
A nice guy, decent, smart, you know?
实话实说  他却不成功  生命到头了
Let's face it-- underachiever, dead-end life, okay?
他罹患癌症  时日无多  加上中年危机
He gets cancer. Time's running out. Midlife crisis.
他承受不了  爆发了  出轨了
He acts up. Steps out.
然后被老婆逮住
Then the wife-- she catches him.
这都是老掉牙的故事了
I mean, it's a story as old as time.
用用脑子吧  玛丽
Look, do the math, Marie.
只有这种可能
Only comes out one way.
看看沃尔特
Knowing Walt, he, uh,
那么内疚  估计是自己向她坦白的
felt so guilty, he probably told her himself.
是吗  我
Yeah, I--
我不知道
I don't know. I think...
如果他出轨了  她应该会告诉我
If he cheated on her, that she would've told me by now.
我就是觉得
It just feels like...
事情比出轨更严重
something more.
是  是  日以继夜  还用问吗
Yes, yes, yes. 24-7 coverage. Need you ask?
还要我怎么做
How much is this gonna run me?
老天  我入错行了
Jesus. I'm in the wrong business.
我再打给你
Yeah. I'll call you.
浪子回头啦
Return of the prodigal.
欢迎回归现实
Welcome back to the land of the living.
-感觉如何  -很好
- How you feeling? - I'm good.
当然如此  世界任你享用
Of course you are. The world's your oyster.
我说得对吗  拥有成堆的现金
Am I right? Unencumbered young man
可以随心所欲的年轻人
with, uh, stacks of cash.
我可嫉妒你了
Hey, I'm, uh-- I'm jealous.
我发誓  绝对是嫉妒了
Hand to God, I'm jealous.
说到现金
Yeah, speaking of cash,
你知道最近谁最让我心痛吗
Uh, you know what's giving me heartburn lately?
你的老搭档  这家伙
Your former partner. This guy...
没命地干  是吧
He works like a bastard, right?
白手起家
Builds a business, single-handed.
结果大生意来了  他呢
Finally, the big money shows up, and what does he do?
他不干了
He walks out.
他有那么高的天赋
Talent like that,
却弃之不用
and he just flushes it down the crapper.
就好像米开朗琪罗不去画画
It's like Michelangelo won't paint.
我知道你洗手不干了
Look, I know you're out of it and all,
但你
But you--
你会和他谈谈的吧
You wouldn't talk to him, would you?
帮助他清醒过来
I mean, help him pull his head out of his ass?
好吧  好吧  不管他了
Alright. Alright, stretch that.
他不会听我的  也不会听你的
He won't listen to me, he's not gonna listen to you,
无意冒犯
All due respect.
你想要工作吗
You want a job?
工作
A job?
谁要找我
Who's got a job for me?
我
I do.
我是想
Thought I'd, uh,
来看看  你不介意的话
Well, visit, if you don't mind.
当然不介意  你不
No, of course not. You don't, uh...
-你不需要用这间房间吧  -不用
- You don't need the room, do you?  - No.
我的东西摊得比较开
I just needed some more space to spread out.
我来看看小霍莉
Just wanted to say hello to little Holly here.
嘿  小姑娘  你好啊
Hey, girl. Hi.
没事啦  高兴点儿
Oh, it's okay. It's okay, it's okay.
这就对了
Oh, yeah.
真是个小美人  你看她
She is a beauty. Look at her.
谢谢你通融让我带她来
Hey, thanks for being so flexible on me coming in.
我只是希望你能全心投入工作
Well, I just wish we had you back full time.
你们也给这里带来许多朝气
You do brighten up the place.
听我说  相信我
Listen, believe me, this is, uh...
我不想这样
I don't wanna bring this up,
但是  这些季度报表我不能签
but I... I can't sign off on these quarterlies.
对不起  真的不能签
I'm sorry. I just can't.
有问题吗
Is that right?
就算你真的要这样做  泰德
If you're gonna do this, Ted,
也不能如此明目张胆
you can't be so glaring about it.
明目张胆
Glaring.
好吧
Okay.
听起来蛮严重
That does sound bad.
跟我说说是什么问题
Uh, show me what's bothering you.
凯勒
Keller.
不
No.
又是
Again...
我很抱歉
God, I'm sorry.
我知道你的感受
I know how you feel about this.
不明来源收入
Revenue with no backup.
这里  这里  还有这里
Here, here, and here.
我都不知道该怎么说
I don't even know what to say.
好吧  这个可以修正的  是吧
Okay. This is- This is fixable, right?
你看我把两万八千八百元销掉
How about if I just push, uh, 28,800,
延到下季度如何
um, out of this into next quarter?
那样的话你可以签吗
Would you sign it then?
我  呃
I'm--
我得说
I'm just saying
我不能签  因为这笔收入现在已经存在了
I can't sign it as it currently exists.
那好吧
Fair enough.
我自己处理
I'll take care of it.
多谢你预先通知我
Thank you for the heads-up.
这种事以后不会再发生了  我保证
Well, you won't have to deal with this again, I swear.
如果你的孩子们知道了怎么办
What if your kids found out?
我的孩子们知道什么
If my kids found out?
你做的这些事
This... what you're doing.
总有一天  他们会长大
I mean, someday, they're gonna be old enough.
你怎么对他们解释
How would you explain it to them?
你这是为难我呀  为什么呢
Put me on the spot, why don't you?
我想  我或许
I guess maybe I'd, um...
我想  我或许是有污点
I'd say that, uh, I might have feet of clay that...
但是我所做的一切  都是为了他们
But that whatever I did, I did thinking of them.
知道吗  是为了更好地培养他们
You know? Trying to provide.
我会让他们
And, uh, I'd ask them
尽量花些时间去了解
to try to take the time to understand...
你知道吗  事实上
You know what? Truth is,
我还没有想过那么远  斯凯勒
I haven't thought that far ahead, Skyler.
我一直是在奋力挣扎  所以
I'm just trying to keep my head above water, so...
我该回去了
I better get back to it.
上帝啊
Oh, God.
嗨  沃尔特  听我说
Hi, Walt. Listen.
我现在不方便讲话  我在工作
I'm... I can't talk- I'm at work right now.
什么
What?
路易斯开车送他来的  我到家的时候他已经在了
Louis dropped him off. He was here when I got home.
不  不  当然不  他得回去
No, no, no. Of course. No. He's not staying.
他明白的
He understands that.
你要我送他到哪里都可以
I'll... I'll bring him anywhere you want.
爸
Dad...
那个  现在是交通高峰
Well, yeah, it is rush hour.
我是说  我当然可以逆着车流
I mean, I could fight traffic
送他去贝内克家
and bring him down to Beneke now,
但如果我们...  岂不是更方便
but wouldn't it be easier if we...
好  好的  很好
Right. Okay. Good.
我们在家等你
So we'll meet you at the house.
好的  再见
Okay. Bye.
你为什么这么做
W-Why are you doing this?
她不让我见你
She's just trying to k-keep me from seeing you,
你却帮着她
and you're helping her.
不  不是这样的  儿子
No. No, son. I mean, your--
你妈妈...  她是有理由的
your mother... she has her reasons.
什么理由
What reasons?
就是
They're, uh...
Well, they're...
这个不太好讲  但是
Well, they're just a little difficult to delineate, but--
我是说  每件事情都是有
I mean, yes, there are two sides to every story.
两个方面的
Always. But, uh,
她呢
she, uh...
现在只能这样
This is just how it has to be.
暂时的  好吗
For now. Okay?
听我说  家毕竟是家
And, look, your home is your home,
你属于那里  好不好
and that is where you belong, okay?
可是你也属于那里
But it's where you belong.
爸  那是你的家
Dad, it... it's your house.
汉克姨夫  玛丽姨妈
Uncle Hank, Aunt Marie--
所有人都知道你没有做错
everybody knows that you hen't done
任何事情
anything wrong.
大家都站在你这一边
Everybody is on your side.
这个  这
Well, it's... it's...
这不是哪一边的问题
it's not about taking sides, though.
你怎么  你怎么能让她这样对你
How can... How can you let her treat you like this?
-好了  -你  你怎么
- Now, come on. - How... How...
怎么可以听之任之
How can you just... just take it?
听我说  好不好  无论怎样
Just listen to me, okay? No matter what,
这些事情绝不会影响到
all of this has nothing to do
我们对你的感情
with how we feel about you, okay?
我们俩都非常非常的爱你  知道吗
We both love you very, very much, okay?
你和你妹妹永远都是第一位的  永远
You and your sister will come first, always.
别难过了
Now, come on.
让我们
Let's, uh...
乐观地看待这件事
Let's try to see this in a positive light, okay?
我们两个都要
Both of us.
振作起来
Let's just buck up.
然后我送你回家
Then I'll take you home.
我得先
Uh, let me first just
去下这老旧的卫生间
hit the old bathroom here.
你好
Hello.
下午好  很高兴见到你们
Good afternoon. Nice to meet you.
-索尔·古德曼  -很高兴见到你
- Saul Goodman. - Nice to meet you.
你不会就是夜间广告里的那个律师吧
You're not that lawyer on late-night television, are you?
快打电话给索尔!
Better call Saul!
我的口头禅哦
I get it all the time.
我们来此是就马戈街9809号房屋出售一事
We're here to discuss the sale of the property
进行磋商
at 9809 Margo.
我知道  老客户了  是吧
I get it. Flat-fee clients. Am I right?
好了  伙计们  你们今天交好运了
Well, folks, today's your lucky day.
我所代理的客户不愿透露姓名
I represent a client who shall remain nameless.
况且  对我们而言
However, for our purposes, you might just as well
赚大钱才是重点
visualize a large bag of money.
他希望在今天通过现金交付购置你们的房产
This individual wants to buy your house today, for cash.
-现金交付  -我理解  在此种经济环境下
- Cash? - Cash. I know. In this economy.
事实上  我客户
In fact, the money is
账户上的余额已所剩无几
already burning a hole in my client's account.
就这点你可以咨询加德纳先生
You can ask Mr. Gardiner.
我已经把账务明细给他看过了
I've shown him all the pertinent financials.
这也是为何我们坐在这里的原因
It the only reason we're sitting here.
很好
Fair enough.
我们需要签订一些合同并进行公证
We, uh, get a few papers signed and notarized,
现在就可以进行
we can take care of this right now.
我也会在今天下午将钱汇给你们
In fact, I can wire you your money this very afternoon.
但唯一值得商榷的是
There's just one little hair in the soup--
价格
uh, the price.
我们觉得87.5万很合理
We feel 875 is very fair.
但我想或许还有点回旋余地
But I suppose there's always a little, uh, wiggle room.
那么就40万
Well, you wiggle us on down to 400,
你们商量下吧
and you got yourselves a deal.
40万  开什么玩笑
400,000? What is that, a joke?
不是  这是我的报价
No, that's my offer.
还不到一半的价钱
That's less than half price.
光翻新就差不多花了那么多
We put almost that much into the renovations alone.
我们就别再讨价还价了
Why don't we just cut the clown act
你就报个实价吧
and you tell us what you're willing to come up to?
40万  这是我最后的报价
400,000. That's my final offer.
-真是浪费时间  -无稽之谈
- Well, this is a waste of time. - Ridiculous.
你怎么会觉得
How could you possibly imagine
-我们会接受这个报价呢  -得了吧  杭
- that we would entertain this? - Come on, Hon.
我也不清楚  只是在听闻制毒室后
I don't know. I just thought some allowance was in order
觉得能在价格上有所减让
once I heard about the meth lab.
该实验室据说在地下室
The one that used to be in the basement.
我看了下你们签署的告知声明
I looked over your signed disclosure statements,
并没有提到制毒室
and I don't see any mention of a meth lab.
没有  没有  在这里提到了白蚁检测
No. No. Oh, you got your termite inspection.
这个不错  但还是没有制毒室
That's good. But no meth lab.
有人会将掩盖重罪的行为
Now, some would call that fraud
称之为欺诈
in service of concealing a felony.
我则是个开明的人
I, myself, am more open-minded.
但这事有点棘手
But it is tricky.
别误会  我很赞同你们的作法
Don't get me wrong. I applaud your c--.
我是指  向买家隐瞒
I mean, good try in sneaking
该房子曾用于制毒这招很聪明
a meth-contaminated property past the buyer.
可以卖个好价钱
I mean, you know, could've been a good deal for you.
太可惜了  如今我可以
Too bad. Now, I could
提起诉讼  将此房产无期限扣押
file a suit and encumber this property indefinitely,
我也可以提起刑事诉讼
or I could start some criminal proceedings.
但这都是你我所不乐于见到的
But I don't think any of us want that now, do we?
怎么样  顾问  你同意吗
How about it, counselor? Do you concur?
到了
Ta-da.
拿好  儿子
Here you go, son.
好了  这里又不是魔鬼岛
Come on. It's not Devil's Island.
行了
Okay. Ooh.
我们到了
Here we go.
好啊
Oh. Hey.
你好
Hello.
我带了披萨来
Uh, mmm. Brought pizza.
是啊  可是我在做饭了
Yeah. Well, I'm making dinner.
好吧  那放冰箱里吧
Oh, okay. I'll just, uh, put it in the fridge.
第二天吃更可口
It's even better the next day, huh?
你来啦  宝贝
Hi, honey.
抱歉
Sorry.
是啊
Yeah.
好吧  斯凯勒
All right. Skyler...
亲爱的  我们楞在这里算怎么回事
Honey, what kind of example do we want to set here?
对吧  我们不能坐下来
Right? I mean, can't we at least just sit down
一起吃块披萨吗
and eat a piece of pizza together?
不能像成年人一样处理问题吗
Just to hash things out like adults? You know--
需要讨论的
We have...discussed
我们都已经讨论过了
everything we need to discuss.
我想我已经说得很清楚了
I thought I made myself very clear.
我放下就走
I got dipping sticks.
这是沃尔特的临时号码
You've reached Walt's temporary number.
请留言
Please leave a message.
今早我出去拿报纸
When I went out this morning to get the newspaper,
发现屋顶上有张披萨
I saw a pizza on our roof.
你知道是怎么回事吗
Would you know anything about that?
听我说  沃尔特  学会控制自己
Listen to me, Walt. You need to control yourself.
冷静下来  接受现实
Calm down, accept the situation,
离我们远点
and keep your distance.
要是你做不到  我就去申请限制令
If you can't manage that, I will get a restraining order.
斯凯勒  斯凯勒
Skyler. Skyler.
我已经收到你的限制令了
I got your restraining order right here!
被禁锢在这里
Restrain this!
不赔不赚也不错
Breaking even's not so bad.
在这种经济环境下  很多人
In this economy, a lot of people
都赔得精光
would kill to break even.
可怜的杰克  要是他知道了
Poor Jake. He had his heart set
该多么地伤心
on going to space camp.
不是吧
Oh, no.
天啊  说曹操曹操到
Oh, G--. This is all we need.
老爸  老妈
Hey, Mom, Dad.
你们还好吗
How's it going?
杰西
Uh, Jesse, it's, uh,
你来得真不巧
really not a good time.
杰西  房子卖掉了
Jesse, the house has been sold.
新房东随时会来
The new owners are expected at any moment.
-你这是去哪里  -进屋
- Where do you think you're going? - Inside.
这房子是我买的
I bought the place.
7点准时回家好吗
Be back by 7, okay?
我爱你
I love you.
再见
Bye.
老天
Jeez.
操  不
Oh, shit. No!
上帝
Oh, God.
它已干涸
It was dead
♪ You see, I've been through the desert ♪
♪ on a horse with no name ♪
♪ It felt good to get out of the rain ♪
♪ in the desert ♪
是我  有些事要告诉你
It's me. There's something you should know about.
稍等
Hold on.